[
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6.3 + 6.2?",
    "answers": [
      "6.14",
      "12.5",
      "7.06",
      "15.69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 23 - 9?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "-9",
      "4",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10.8 + 6.5?",
    "answers": [
      "17.3",
      "35.34",
      "32.28",
      "15.56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "2:9",
      "4:9",
      "2:10",
      "3:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 - 15?",
    "answers": [
      "-7",
      "-8",
      "-13",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -6 - 8?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "0",
      "29",
      "-14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.9 + 18.8?",
    "answers": [
      "26.93",
      "36.7",
      "40.87",
      "21.89"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13.3 + 12.7?",
    "answers": [
      "26.0",
      "34.73",
      "40.24",
      "26.87"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 0.7 + 9.6?",
    "answers": [
      "22.16",
      "10.3",
      "13.64",
      "5.09"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13.1 + 10.1?",
    "answers": [
      "23.2",
      "33.35",
      "3.76",
      "20.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.5 + 19.3?",
    "answers": [
      "18.97",
      "36.8",
      "41.75",
      "19.05"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/9 + 9/3?",
    "answers": [
      "420/108",
      "315/81",
      "105/27",
      "210/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "105/27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/7 + 2/8?",
    "answers": [
      "210/168",
      "70/56",
      "140/112",
      "280/224"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70/56"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14.9 + 17.2?",
    "answers": [
      "35.95",
      "41.22",
      "28.05",
      "32.1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "8:10",
      "7:10",
      "6:11",
      "6:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "6:4",
      "7:4",
      "6:5",
      "8:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/2 + 2/5?",
    "answers": [
      "132/30",
      "44/10",
      "176/40",
      "88/20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44/10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "2:2",
      "3:2",
      "2:3",
      "4:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 5 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "7:5",
      "5:6",
      "6:5",
      "5:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/4 + 5/5?",
    "answers": [
      "120/40",
      "60/20",
      "180/60",
      "240/80"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 27 - 15?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "12",
      "7",
      "33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/9 + 6/8?",
    "answers": [
      "204/144",
      "102/72",
      "408/288",
      "306/216"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "102/72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7.9 + 2.9?",
    "answers": [
      "22.09",
      "18.78",
      "10.8",
      "17.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.5 + 10.1?",
    "answers": [
      "25.6",
      "23.49",
      "13.73",
      "41.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14.6 + 2.5?",
    "answers": [
      "4.5",
      "24.18",
      "17.1",
      "0.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14.7 + 10.0?",
    "answers": [
      "44.28",
      "29.57",
      "25.35",
      "24.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -12 + 1?",
    "answers": [
      "-4",
      "-59",
      "34",
      "-11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.7 + 7.8?",
    "answers": [
      "21.55",
      "8.47",
      "6.1",
      "17.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "3:9",
      "5:9",
      "4:9",
      "3:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -10 + 21?",
    "answers": [
      "25",
      "-21",
      "11",
      "-29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5 + -10?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "13",
      "-5",
      "-8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 0 - 29?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "-29",
      "-74",
      "-56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-29"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "3:10",
      "2:10",
      "1:11",
      "1:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -7 - 6?",
    "answers": [
      "24",
      "-58",
      "-47",
      "-13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -17 - -1?",
    "answers": [
      "-59",
      "33",
      "-29",
      "-16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/5 + 8/8?",
    "answers": [
      "144/80",
      "288/160",
      "72/40",
      "216/120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72/40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 5 to 3?",
    "answers": [
      "5:4",
      "5:3",
      "7:3",
      "6:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5:3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/4 + 3/5?",
    "answers": [
      "66/60",
      "44/40",
      "88/80",
      "22/20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 + 10?",
    "answers": [
      "33",
      "21",
      "-22",
      "40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.9 + 6.8?",
    "answers": [
      "18.7",
      "31.24",
      "31.03",
      "29.74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -5 + 2?",
    "answers": [
      "-3",
      "-42",
      "-16",
      "-28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.8 + 17.4?",
    "answers": [
      "20.02",
      "3.23",
      "20.2",
      "7.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "10:6",
      "11:6",
      "10:7",
      "12:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/9 + 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "156/18",
      "234/27",
      "312/36",
      "78/9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "78/9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/5 + 8/4?",
    "answers": [
      "156/60",
      "104/40",
      "52/20",
      "208/80"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "52/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/5 + 4/4?",
    "answers": [
      "96/60",
      "32/20",
      "64/40",
      "128/80"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/5 + 3/7?",
    "answers": [
      "86/70",
      "172/140",
      "129/105",
      "43/35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "43/35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/4 + 7/9?",
    "answers": [
      "182/72",
      "273/108",
      "91/36",
      "364/144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "91/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "2:6",
      "2:5",
      "3:5",
      "4:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 + -7?",
    "answers": [
      "-14",
      "-4",
      "8",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/9 + 2/1?",
    "answers": [
      "48/18",
      "24/9",
      "96/36",
      "72/27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24/9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4.6 + 8.5?",
    "answers": [
      "2.02",
      "29.62",
      "15.98",
      "13.1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "9:9",
      "7:10",
      "7:9",
      "8:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/3 + 2/2?",
    "answers": [
      "36/18",
      "24/12",
      "12/6",
      "48/24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 + 8?",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "19",
      "26",
      "-18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/3 + 7/5?",
    "answers": [
      "46/15",
      "92/30",
      "184/60",
      "138/45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "46/15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -17 - 19?",
    "answers": [
      "-79",
      "-72",
      "-36",
      "-7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -20 - 4?",
    "answers": [
      "-24",
      "3",
      "9",
      "-66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -15 + 14?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "-1",
      "20",
      "-37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.1 + 0.6?",
    "answers": [
      "25.41",
      "8.7",
      "24.97",
      "10.8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "3:5",
      "2:5",
      "1:5",
      "1:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "6:6",
      "8:5",
      "6:5",
      "7:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/8 + 5/8?",
    "answers": [
      "144/128",
      "216/192",
      "288/256",
      "72/64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72/64"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.5 + 6.0?",
    "answers": [
      "7.26",
      "8.5",
      "12.77",
      "15.45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/7 + 3/1?",
    "answers": [
      "84/21",
      "28/7",
      "112/28",
      "56/14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28/7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -15 + 8?",
    "answers": [
      "24",
      "-56",
      "-15",
      "-7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.5 + 14.4?",
    "answers": [
      "33.57",
      "35.16",
      "23.9",
      "7.97"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -2 - -3?",
    "answers": [
      "-20",
      "17",
      "1",
      "-17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 29 + -15?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "59",
      "11",
      "-11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "10:6",
      "10:5",
      "12:5",
      "11:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/6 + 1/1?",
    "answers": [
      "8/6",
      "32/24",
      "24/18",
      "16/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6.3 + 10.1?",
    "answers": [
      "19.24",
      "35.19",
      "16.4",
      "33.61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.8 + 8.8?",
    "answers": [
      "11.6",
      "18.58",
      "15.51",
      "7.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/3 + 9/6?",
    "answers": [
      "69/18",
      "138/36",
      "276/72",
      "207/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "69/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 5 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "5:2",
      "7:1",
      "6:1",
      "5:1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1 - 25?",
    "answers": [
      "-61",
      "-4",
      "-24",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/6 + 2/1?",
    "answers": [
      "76/24",
      "19/6",
      "57/18",
      "38/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/1 + 7/8?",
    "answers": [
      "39/8",
      "78/16",
      "117/24",
      "156/32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "39/8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "8:4",
      "6:4",
      "7:4",
      "6:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/4 + 4/9?",
    "answers": [
      "172/144",
      "129/108",
      "43/36",
      "86/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "43/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "11:6",
      "10:7",
      "12:6",
      "10:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/7 + 2/7?",
    "answers": [
      "140/196",
      "105/147",
      "70/98",
      "35/49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35/49"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -19 + 3?",
    "answers": [
      "-38",
      "-16",
      "29",
      "-15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.0 + 3.7?",
    "answers": [
      "14.7",
      "8.97",
      "6.02",
      "5.95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 0.9 + 14.8?",
    "answers": [
      "2.46",
      "2.52",
      "1.84",
      "15.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 + -14?",
    "answers": [
      "-41",
      "38",
      "7",
      "-6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/2 + 7/9?",
    "answers": [
      "154/36",
      "308/72",
      "77/18",
      "231/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "77/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/6 + 1/1?",
    "answers": [
      "32/24",
      "8/6",
      "16/12",
      "24/18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/9 + 8/2?",
    "answers": [
      "76/18",
      "304/72",
      "152/36",
      "228/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "76/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "5:9",
      "4:10",
      "4:9",
      "6:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "3:5",
      "3:4",
      "5:4",
      "4:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "7:7",
      "7:6",
      "8:6",
      "9:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -13 - 10?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "-23",
      "-66",
      "-57"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-23"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -8 - -8?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "0",
      "-17",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 30 + -3?",
    "answers": [
      "27",
      "48",
      "1",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7.5 + 15.3?",
    "answers": [
      "19.46",
      "7.75",
      "22.8",
      "24.61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 + 23?",
    "answers": [
      "38",
      "66",
      "-1",
      "53"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "38"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/7 + 1/9?",
    "answers": [
      "264/189",
      "88/63",
      "352/252",
      "176/126"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "88/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.0 + 5.9?",
    "answers": [
      "30.96",
      "24.81",
      "22.9",
      "42.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "4:6",
      "5:6",
      "3:7",
      "3:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12.5 + 7.3?",
    "answers": [
      "12.34",
      "14.84",
      "24.09",
      "19.8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/3 + 4/2?",
    "answers": [
      "32/12",
      "16/6",
      "64/24",
      "48/18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "2:10",
      "1:11",
      "3:10",
      "1:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.9 + 4.8?",
    "answers": [
      "15.48",
      "27.52",
      "20.13",
      "7.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "8:5",
      "9:5",
      "7:5",
      "7:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/2 + 3/7?",
    "answers": [
      "96/28",
      "48/14",
      "192/56",
      "144/42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 9 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "10:6",
      "9:7",
      "9:6",
      "11:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "6:1",
      "4:1",
      "5:1",
      "4:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.8 + 3.6?",
    "answers": [
      "13.4",
      "7.4",
      "19.31",
      "19.92"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5.7 + 10.6?",
    "answers": [
      "16.3",
      "22.8",
      "13.33",
      "26.53"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.0 + 3.4?",
    "answers": [
      "12.4",
      "2.56",
      "7.12",
      "14.76"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7.2 + 16.6?",
    "answers": [
      "23.8",
      "36.53",
      "5.32",
      "26.47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.7 + 18.5?",
    "answers": [
      "35.41",
      "47.96",
      "38.2",
      "34.37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "38.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 8?",
    "answers": [
      "5:8",
      "4:9",
      "6:8",
      "4:8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/3 + 2/2?",
    "answers": [
      "72/24",
      "36/12",
      "54/18",
      "18/6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.5 + 1.5?",
    "answers": [
      "10.4",
      "22.75",
      "5.0",
      "12.08"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/9 + 3/2?",
    "answers": [
      "66/36",
      "99/54",
      "33/18",
      "132/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 8?",
    "answers": [
      "10:8",
      "10:9",
      "11:8",
      "12:8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.9 + 4.2?",
    "answers": [
      "20.35",
      "1.26",
      "0.2",
      "8.1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 3?",
    "answers": [
      "4:3",
      "5:3",
      "3:3",
      "3:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "2:1",
      "1:2",
      "1:1",
      "3:1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "3:4",
      "3:5",
      "4:4",
      "5:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13.9 + 13.9?",
    "answers": [
      "27.8",
      "45.32",
      "36.78",
      "26.15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6.8 + 1.2?",
    "answers": [
      "8.0",
      "23.69",
      "5.54",
      "1.29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/5 + 3/6?",
    "answers": [
      "42/60",
      "84/120",
      "21/30",
      "63/90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21/30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1.7 + 11.8?",
    "answers": [
      "8.86",
      "13.5",
      "16.68",
      "9.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/3 + 9/4?",
    "answers": [
      "189/36",
      "63/12",
      "126/24",
      "252/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 + 3/9?",
    "answers": [
      "60/72",
      "30/36",
      "45/54",
      "15/18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/1 + 6/5?",
    "answers": [
      "22/10",
      "11/5",
      "33/15",
      "44/20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11/5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14 + 26?",
    "answers": [
      "40",
      "43",
      "81",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -14 - -12?",
    "answers": [
      "-51",
      "-2",
      "4",
      "-8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 8 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "8:7",
      "8:8",
      "9:7",
      "10:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.8 + 5.6?",
    "answers": [
      "25.4",
      "10.86",
      "5.88",
      "21.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -13 + -16?",
    "answers": [
      "-50",
      "-21",
      "-62",
      "-29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-29"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/4 + 4/5?",
    "answers": [
      "42/40",
      "63/60",
      "21/20",
      "84/80"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -15 - 8?",
    "answers": [
      "-23",
      "21",
      "16",
      "-12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-23"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/1 + 8/3?",
    "answers": [
      "14/3",
      "56/12",
      "42/9",
      "28/6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.7 + 0.4?",
    "answers": [
      "24.09",
      "14.37",
      "14.84",
      "10.1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.5 + 5.5?",
    "answers": [
      "17.91",
      "9.0",
      "21.43",
      "2.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/2 + 8/2?",
    "answers": [
      "32/4",
      "64/8",
      "128/16",
      "96/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32/4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/8 + 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "195/24",
      "65/8",
      "130/16",
      "260/32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "65/8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "1:5",
      "2:5",
      "1:6",
      "3:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/3 + 1/6?",
    "answers": [
      "153/54",
      "204/72",
      "51/18",
      "102/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "51/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/2 + 8/3?",
    "answers": [
      "88/24",
      "66/18",
      "44/12",
      "22/6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/3 + 2/7?",
    "answers": [
      "69/21",
      "207/63",
      "138/42",
      "276/84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "69/21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/5 + 6/5?",
    "answers": [
      "180/100",
      "45/25",
      "135/75",
      "90/50"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45/25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "1:7",
      "2:7",
      "3:7",
      "1:8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.6 + 16.0?",
    "answers": [
      "18.8",
      "35.72",
      "33.6",
      "52.88"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16.7 + 5.8?",
    "answers": [
      "33.51",
      "31.97",
      "22.5",
      "41.33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "7:10",
      "8:10",
      "9:10",
      "7:11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/8 + 9/5?",
    "answers": [
      "224/80",
      "112/40",
      "448/160",
      "336/120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "112/40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 + 6/2?",
    "answers": [
      "48/12",
      "192/48",
      "96/24",
      "144/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6.4 + 0.1?",
    "answers": [
      "6.5",
      "7.75",
      "0.74",
      "19.2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "3:10",
      "5:10",
      "3:11",
      "4:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 + 11?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "23",
      "29",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "29"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/9 + 2/7?",
    "answers": [
      "92/126",
      "138/189",
      "184/252",
      "46/63"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "46/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4 + 15?",
    "answers": [
      "66",
      "-9",
      "19",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "1:2",
      "3:1",
      "2:1",
      "1:1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 8?",
    "answers": [
      "4:8",
      "5:8",
      "3:9",
      "3:8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.8 + 7.5?",
    "answers": [
      "6.89",
      "8.97",
      "19.3",
      "7.8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3 + 14?",
    "answers": [
      "-12",
      "17",
      "-11",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/9 + 4/3?",
    "answers": [
      "192/108",
      "96/54",
      "48/27",
      "144/81"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/8 + 4/4?",
    "answers": [
      "272/128",
      "68/32",
      "204/96",
      "136/64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "68/32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14.3 + 4.3?",
    "answers": [
      "4.55",
      "15.45",
      "11.81",
      "18.6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 9 to 6?",
    "answers": [
      "9:7",
      "9:6",
      "11:6",
      "10:6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9:6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 12.5 + 15.7?",
    "answers": [
      "13.45",
      "40.71",
      "28.2",
      "22.6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 - 23?",
    "answers": [
      "-5",
      "-1",
      "31",
      "-31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/4 + 5/3?",
    "answers": [
      "44/12",
      "176/48",
      "88/24",
      "132/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/7 + 6/6?",
    "answers": [
      "48/42",
      "192/168",
      "96/84",
      "144/126"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/7 + 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "64/7",
      "192/21",
      "256/28",
      "128/14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "64/7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8 - -1?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "9",
      "-8",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "11:2",
      "10:3",
      "10:2",
      "12:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.7 + 8.0?",
    "answers": [
      "23.7",
      "22.31",
      "20.12",
      "14.94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "9:2",
      "8:2",
      "7:2",
      "7:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/9 + 3/9?",
    "answers": [
      "288/324",
      "144/162",
      "72/81",
      "216/243"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72/81"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.8 + 20.0?",
    "answers": [
      "33.8",
      "30.26",
      "28.8",
      "16.3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 27 - -14?",
    "answers": [
      "22",
      "6",
      "41",
      "90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "41"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.9 + 11.7?",
    "answers": [
      "14.24",
      "24.51",
      "27.6",
      "37.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.4 + 2.9?",
    "answers": [
      "20.16",
      "5.3",
      "15.52",
      "20.19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "2:4",
      "3:4",
      "2:5",
      "4:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5.5 + 5.3?",
    "answers": [
      "26.11",
      "26.48",
      "10.8",
      "25.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "3:10",
      "3:9",
      "5:9",
      "4:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11 + -1?",
    "answers": [
      "-30",
      "-11",
      "30",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/4 + 5/5?",
    "answers": [
      "90/40",
      "135/60",
      "45/20",
      "180/80"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45/20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/9 + 2/3?",
    "answers": [
      "39/27",
      "117/81",
      "156/108",
      "78/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "39/27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 + -10?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "5",
      "-44",
      "-3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "2:2",
      "3:2",
      "4:2",
      "2:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "8:7",
      "7:7",
      "6:8",
      "6:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.2 + 13.5?",
    "answers": [
      "41.17",
      "40.21",
      "24.7",
      "26.43"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.8 + 15.2?",
    "answers": [
      "28.39",
      "19.0",
      "38.24",
      "17.59"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.5 + 3.0?",
    "answers": [
      "23.77",
      "16.07",
      "24.32",
      "20.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7.2 + 5.6?",
    "answers": [
      "12.8",
      "25.97",
      "8.5",
      "20.46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "11:2",
      "10:2",
      "12:2",
      "10:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/7 + 4/4?",
    "answers": [
      "144/84",
      "48/28",
      "96/56",
      "192/112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.9 + 17.1?",
    "answers": [
      "15.62",
      "33.0",
      "50.98",
      "26.07"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 + 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "34/4",
      "68/8",
      "51/6",
      "17/2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/4 + 3/8?",
    "answers": [
      "180/96",
      "120/64",
      "240/128",
      "60/32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60/32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -17 + -19?",
    "answers": [
      "-76",
      "-36",
      "-35",
      "-6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9.8 + 16.9?",
    "answers": [
      "24.54",
      "21.65",
      "29.09",
      "26.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -12 - 15?",
    "answers": [
      "-19",
      "-27",
      "-59",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 + 1/6?",
    "answers": [
      "168/144",
      "126/108",
      "42/36",
      "84/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/8 + 3/4?",
    "answers": [
      "108/96",
      "36/32",
      "72/64",
      "144/128"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36/32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "4:4",
      "2:4",
      "2:5",
      "3:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19 + -5?",
    "answers": [
      "28",
      "-19",
      "4",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/7 + 4/4?",
    "answers": [
      "120/56",
      "60/28",
      "180/84",
      "240/112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60/28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/6 + 7/1?",
    "answers": [
      "50/6",
      "100/12",
      "150/18",
      "200/24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -12 + 16?",
    "answers": [
      "27",
      "4",
      "-6",
      "-29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/8 + 1/2?",
    "answers": [
      "44/32",
      "66/48",
      "88/64",
      "22/16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22/16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 5 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "5:6",
      "5:5",
      "7:5",
      "6:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/8 + 1/4?",
    "answers": [
      "128/128",
      "96/96",
      "64/64",
      "32/32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32/32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 9 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "9:4",
      "10:4",
      "9:5",
      "11:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "2:6",
      "3:5",
      "2:5",
      "4:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/1 + 9/3?",
    "answers": [
      "81/9",
      "27/3",
      "54/6",
      "108/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27/3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.6 + 12.3?",
    "answers": [
      "15.34",
      "31.83",
      "41.97",
      "31.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "31.9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.3 + 2.1?",
    "answers": [
      "4.4",
      "18.77",
      "0.86",
      "8.47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6.5 + 3.8?",
    "answers": [
      "23.23",
      "26.54",
      "10.3",
      "17.03"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.2 + 16.2?",
    "answers": [
      "19.4",
      "27.18",
      "8.78",
      "33.61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 29 + 11?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "-7",
      "40",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19 - 6?",
    "answers": [
      "-33",
      "49",
      "13",
      "-4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 - 18?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "-29",
      "51",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10.1 + 8.6?",
    "answers": [
      "16.03",
      "11.29",
      "18.7",
      "14.95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 8 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "10:10",
      "8:11",
      "9:10",
      "8:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1.8 + 16.2?",
    "answers": [
      "18.0",
      "24.22",
      "0.66",
      "25.29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "7:5",
      "9:4",
      "8:4",
      "7:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -14 - 27?",
    "answers": [
      "-29",
      "-41",
      "-47",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-41"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5.2 + 8.2?",
    "answers": [
      "13.4",
      "27.54",
      "15.74",
      "18.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 4?",
    "answers": [
      "4:4",
      "5:4",
      "6:4",
      "4:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 10 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "10:1",
      "12:1",
      "11:1",
      "10:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "9:7",
      "7:7",
      "7:8",
      "8:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -4 - 16?",
    "answers": [
      "-18",
      "-62",
      "-20",
      "-7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17 - 27?",
    "answers": [
      "-37",
      "-10",
      "-56",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/7 + 6/7?",
    "answers": [
      "252/147",
      "84/49",
      "336/196",
      "168/98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84/49"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/4 + 6/3?",
    "answers": [
      "66/24",
      "132/48",
      "33/12",
      "99/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "5:10",
      "4:10",
      "3:10",
      "3:11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "6:10",
      "5:10",
      "4:10",
      "4:11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.8 + 14.0?",
    "answers": [
      "8.14",
      "22.8",
      "40.16",
      "28.26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "3:9",
      "1:9",
      "2:9",
      "1:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -2 - -11?",
    "answers": [
      "-7",
      "9",
      "21",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.7 + 3.4?",
    "answers": [
      "15.23",
      "12.1",
      "16.73",
      "1.88"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 3?",
    "answers": [
      "3:3",
      "1:3",
      "2:3",
      "1:4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/7 + 6/9?",
    "answers": [
      "120/126",
      "60/63",
      "240/252",
      "180/189"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 30 + 13?",
    "answers": [
      "87",
      "43",
      "54",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "43"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 - 21?",
    "answers": [
      "-15",
      "-23",
      "-48",
      "-9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 + -11?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "38",
      "27",
      "-37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 28 + -12?",
    "answers": [
      "39",
      "16",
      "21",
      "-2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 9 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "9:8",
      "11:7",
      "9:7",
      "10:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/4 + 3/7?",
    "answers": [
      "52/56",
      "78/84",
      "104/112",
      "26/28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26/28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.8 + 18.7?",
    "answers": [
      "24.66",
      "22.56",
      "50.38",
      "36.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.7 + 3.8?",
    "answers": [
      "4.13",
      "32.42",
      "15.5",
      "2.05"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 9 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "9:8",
      "11:7",
      "10:7",
      "9:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5.5 + 10.6?",
    "answers": [
      "16.1",
      "1.29",
      "27.96",
      "13.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 21 - -8?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "41",
      "63",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "29"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/2 + 7/5?",
    "answers": [
      "68/20",
      "136/40",
      "102/30",
      "34/10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "34/10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/7 + 7/5?",
    "answers": [
      "74/35",
      "222/105",
      "296/140",
      "148/70"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "74/35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "3:1",
      "2:1",
      "1:2",
      "1:1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.0 + 19.4?",
    "answers": [
      "18.63",
      "27.4",
      "42.63",
      "31.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27.4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7 + 21?",
    "answers": [
      "54",
      "-19",
      "28",
      "-9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 26 - -10?",
    "answers": [
      "41",
      "-7",
      "66",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.4 + 16.7?",
    "answers": [
      "53.47",
      "36.1",
      "43.34",
      "19.82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 16 - 21?",
    "answers": [
      "-5",
      "27",
      "3",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 14.0 + 0.5?",
    "answers": [
      "18.1",
      "14.5",
      "4.18",
      "22.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -4 + -2?",
    "answers": [
      "-31",
      "-53",
      "-6",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8.4 + 17.7?",
    "answers": [
      "26.1",
      "10.36",
      "20.36",
      "13.23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 8 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "9:9",
      "8:9",
      "10:9",
      "8:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/4 + 3/1?",
    "answers": [
      "16/4",
      "64/16",
      "32/8",
      "48/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16/4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.9 + 18.7?",
    "answers": [
      "54.41",
      "38.6",
      "39.72",
      "47.71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "38.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 0 + 28?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "28",
      "-16",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19.0 + 4.0?",
    "answers": [
      "37.76",
      "24.72",
      "23.0",
      "16.71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/7 + 2/6?",
    "answers": [
      "38/42",
      "114/126",
      "152/168",
      "76/84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "38/42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.0 + 7.2?",
    "answers": [
      "22.2",
      "23.32",
      "22.75",
      "21.46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/3 + 5/5?",
    "answers": [
      "180/60",
      "90/30",
      "135/45",
      "45/15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45/15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13.2 + 16.3?",
    "answers": [
      "45.33",
      "37.1",
      "29.5",
      "21.06"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "29.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 - 19?",
    "answers": [
      "-18",
      "-13",
      "-12",
      "-50"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 8 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "10:1",
      "8:2",
      "9:1",
      "8:1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/4 + 6/9?",
    "answers": [
      "315/108",
      "210/72",
      "420/144",
      "105/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "105/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -6 - -7?",
    "answers": [
      "-12",
      "1",
      "45",
      "-3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -2 - 14?",
    "answers": [
      "-1",
      "-16",
      "-57",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 + 3?",
    "answers": [
      "-12",
      "18",
      "-17",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 1 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "2:5",
      "1:6",
      "1:5",
      "3:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13.8 + 18.7?",
    "answers": [
      "29.03",
      "15.57",
      "50.27",
      "32.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2.8 + 16.2?",
    "answers": [
      "19.0",
      "34.9",
      "18.23",
      "19.44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7.0 + 6.0?",
    "answers": [
      "15.07",
      "13.0",
      "11.48",
      "19.98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 10 - 22?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "-42",
      "-12",
      "35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/4 + 6/3?",
    "answers": [
      "144/36",
      "96/24",
      "192/48",
      "48/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 13 - -11?",
    "answers": [
      "69",
      "16",
      "17",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 3?",
    "answers": [
      "6:4",
      "8:3",
      "6:3",
      "7:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 20 - 12?",
    "answers": [
      "-41",
      "8",
      "54",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6 + -15?",
    "answers": [
      "-25",
      "-9",
      "-42",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "6:2",
      "6:3",
      "8:2",
      "7:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15 - 8?",
    "answers": [
      "3",
      "7",
      "-33",
      "50"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -15 - 5?",
    "answers": [
      "1",
      "12",
      "28",
      "-20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "4:9",
      "2:10",
      "3:9",
      "2:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 1?",
    "answers": [
      "3:1",
      "2:1",
      "4:1",
      "2:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.8 + 8.9?",
    "answers": [
      "12.72",
      "9.15",
      "10.69",
      "24.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24.7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 17.5 + 18.0?",
    "answers": [
      "35.5",
      "48.01",
      "44.17",
      "36.42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/8 + 3/9?",
    "answers": [
      "33/72",
      "99/216",
      "132/288",
      "66/144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33/72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -15 - -16?",
    "answers": [
      "46",
      "1",
      "19",
      "-35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -6 - 9?",
    "answers": [
      "-19",
      "-15",
      "-18",
      "-63"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18.2 + 0.8?",
    "answers": [
      "19.0",
      "34.16",
      "28.47",
      "10.62"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/3 + 5/6?",
    "answers": [
      "63/18",
      "189/54",
      "252/72",
      "126/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 7 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "7:5",
      "7:6",
      "8:5",
      "9:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 19 + -7?",
    "answers": [
      "-22",
      "12",
      "-6",
      "60"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -3 - 6?",
    "answers": [
      "30",
      "-9",
      "6",
      "-14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 2?",
    "answers": [
      "4:2",
      "2:3",
      "2:2",
      "3:2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 + 4/3?",
    "answers": [
      "126/54",
      "42/18",
      "168/72",
      "84/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/4 + 4/6?",
    "answers": [
      "34/24",
      "68/48",
      "102/72",
      "136/96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "34/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 30 - 21?",
    "answers": [
      "-27",
      "-28",
      "32",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "8:9",
      "7:9",
      "6:10",
      "6:9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 3 to 7?",
    "answers": [
      "4:7",
      "3:8",
      "3:7",
      "5:7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3:7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 11.8 + 8.2?",
    "answers": [
      "14.14",
      "16.42",
      "20.0",
      "17.51"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 + 4/5?",
    "answers": [
      "58/60",
      "87/90",
      "29/30",
      "116/120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "29/30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -2 - 10?",
    "answers": [
      "24",
      "-35",
      "-12",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/5 + 8/5?",
    "answers": [
      "255/75",
      "170/50",
      "85/25",
      "340/100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "85/25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 2 to 10?",
    "answers": [
      "3:10",
      "2:10",
      "2:11",
      "4:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2:10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18 - -12?",
    "answers": [
      "7",
      "30",
      "-13",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/1 + 2/6?",
    "answers": [
      "52/12",
      "104/24",
      "26/6",
      "78/18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 21 + 9?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "32",
      "50",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 18.9 + 14.6?",
    "answers": [
      "16.62",
      "33.5",
      "18.74",
      "36.24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -9 + 4?",
    "answers": [
      "-46",
      "-5",
      "19",
      "-21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3.9 + 0.4?",
    "answers": [
      "19.76",
      "23.09",
      "4.3",
      "22.08"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/5 + 6/6?",
    "answers": [
      "162/90",
      "108/60",
      "216/120",
      "54/30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54/30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/6 + 6/7?",
    "answers": [
      "92/42",
      "184/84",
      "276/126",
      "368/168"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "92/42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/6 + 1/2?",
    "answers": [
      "14/12",
      "28/24",
      "42/36",
      "56/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 15.6 + 11.6?",
    "answers": [
      "31.97",
      "27.2",
      "14.66",
      "35.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4.0 + 18.1?",
    "answers": [
      "16.33",
      "35.68",
      "32.58",
      "22.1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/7 + 2/4?",
    "answers": [
      "18/28",
      "36/56",
      "72/112",
      "54/84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18/28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 6 to 3?",
    "answers": [
      "6:3",
      "8:3",
      "6:4",
      "7:3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6:3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/1 + 2/2?",
    "answers": [
      "16/8",
      "12/6",
      "8/4",
      "4/2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -19 - -1?",
    "answers": [
      "-54",
      "-28",
      "11",
      "-18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is -17 + -16?",
    "answers": [
      "-22",
      "-33",
      "-4",
      "-26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-33"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 5 to 9?",
    "answers": [
      "5:9",
      "6:9",
      "7:9",
      "5:10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5:9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the ratio 4 to 5?",
    "answers": [
      "4:6",
      "5:5",
      "6:5",
      "4:5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4:5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 0 - 12?",
    "answers": [
      "-40",
      "-12",
      "0",
      "-46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "-12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/3 \u00d7 1/3?",
    "answers": [
      "6/18",
      "9/27",
      "12/36",
      "3/9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3/9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 = 20",
    "answers": [
      "-17",
      "17",
      "28",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [5, 6, 16, 19, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "-7",
      "33",
      "-9",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 7 and width 10?",
    "answers": [
      "70",
      "56",
      "106",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [19, 9, 10, 13, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "-23",
      "61",
      "19",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 14?",
    "answers": [
      "167",
      "110",
      "140",
      "188"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/5 \u00d7 3/1?",
    "answers": [
      "54/15",
      "72/20",
      "36/10",
      "18/5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18/5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 17 and width 5?",
    "answers": [
      "85",
      "116",
      "135",
      "106"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "85"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 10 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "24.65",
      "9.69",
      "10.0",
      "18.83"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 21",
    "answers": [
      "61",
      "-29",
      "-11",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 50 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "48.39",
      "66.39",
      "67.19",
      "50.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 \u00d7 7/8?",
    "answers": [
      "126/144",
      "42/48",
      "168/192",
      "84/96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "246",
      "250",
      "285",
      "240"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 55 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "5.97",
      "5.74",
      "11.0",
      "9.87"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [2, 11, 3, 10, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "11",
      "-32",
      "55",
      "21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 6 = 9",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "-40",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 98 miles in 4 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "18.91",
      "24.5",
      "39.34",
      "4.86"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 7 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "86",
      "76",
      "149",
      "112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "112"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/8 \u00d7 3/6?",
    "answers": [
      "3/48",
      "6/96",
      "12/192",
      "9/144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/8 \u00d7 6/6?",
    "answers": [
      "90/144",
      "30/48",
      "120/192",
      "60/96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 6 = 13",
    "answers": [
      "-16",
      "7",
      "32",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 16 = 21",
    "answers": [
      "-15",
      "-26",
      "-6",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/1 \u00d7 6/5?",
    "answers": [
      "144/15",
      "192/20",
      "48/5",
      "96/10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/9 \u00d7 1/5?",
    "answers": [
      "21/135",
      "7/45",
      "28/180",
      "14/90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7/45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 18 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "263",
      "216",
      "183",
      "206"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/6 \u00d7 6/8?",
    "answers": [
      "12/48",
      "36/144",
      "24/96",
      "48/192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 15?",
    "answers": [
      "92",
      "69",
      "45",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [17, 9, 11, 19, 19]?",
    "answers": [
      "45",
      "47",
      "35",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 5 and width 13?",
    "answers": [
      "65",
      "37",
      "57",
      "43"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "65"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/8 \u00d7 1/7?",
    "answers": [
      "10/112",
      "15/168",
      "5/56",
      "20/224"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5/56"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [3, 20, 1, 18, 16]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "46",
      "52",
      "-11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 = 13",
    "answers": [
      "-18",
      "-6",
      "10",
      "46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 11 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "215",
      "176",
      "178",
      "179"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "176"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "128",
      "83",
      "135",
      "120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "128"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [20, 15, 11, 4, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "-13",
      "-30",
      "20",
      "66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 18 and width 5?",
    "answers": [
      "84",
      "90",
      "89",
      "71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [4, 12, 4, 11, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "-29",
      "-28",
      "17",
      "-33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 5 = 9",
    "answers": [
      "-18",
      "12",
      "4",
      "-9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [13, 19, 15, 14, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "39",
      "61",
      "-20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/8 \u00d7 8/3?",
    "answers": [
      "96/72",
      "32/24",
      "128/96",
      "64/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 19, 2, 8, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "62",
      "68",
      "64",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [14, 3, 9, 18, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "-17",
      "-4",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/9 \u00d7 9/1?",
    "answers": [
      "36/36",
      "27/27",
      "18/18",
      "9/9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 14 = 29",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "48",
      "4",
      "-6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 19 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "21.12",
      "3.8",
      "22.75",
      "8.66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 10 = 16",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "35",
      "6",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 13 = 31",
    "answers": [
      "64",
      "41",
      "6",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 14 miles in 6 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "20.8",
      "21.62",
      "14.87",
      "2.3333333333333335"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.3333333333333335"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 18 and width 10?",
    "answers": [
      "189",
      "191",
      "205",
      "180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "180"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [19, 14, 20, 7, 19]?",
    "answers": [
      "55",
      "26",
      "-23",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 94 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "13.428571428571429",
      "15.64",
      "30.53",
      "5.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 17 and width 8?",
    "answers": [
      "166",
      "113",
      "136",
      "140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "136"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 8 = 10",
    "answers": [
      "-8",
      "-28",
      "5",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 \u00d7 5/8?",
    "answers": [
      "90/144",
      "60/96",
      "30/48",
      "120/192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 11?",
    "answers": [
      "88",
      "112",
      "119",
      "87"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "88"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [20, 6, 9, 6, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "-18",
      "57",
      "20",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [9, 19, 17, 1, 3]?",
    "answers": [
      "61",
      "67",
      "29",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/8 \u00d7 7/3?",
    "answers": [
      "98/48",
      "196/96",
      "49/24",
      "147/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "49/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 6 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "39",
      "42",
      "85"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 \u00d7 1/7?",
    "answers": [
      "3/63",
      "4/84",
      "2/42",
      "1/21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1/21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 4?",
    "answers": [
      "26",
      "32",
      "53",
      "-15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 15 = 22",
    "answers": [
      "-4",
      "-42",
      "46",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/2 \u00d7 2/4?",
    "answers": [
      "24/24",
      "8/8",
      "16/16",
      "32/32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [19, 11, 15, 14, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "4",
      "-24",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "106",
      "87",
      "26",
      "70"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 11 = 20",
    "answers": [
      "-22",
      "12",
      "-26",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 60 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "60.0",
      "42.68",
      "57.38",
      "69.13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 17 and width 2?",
    "answers": [
      "78",
      "34",
      "14",
      "-7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "34"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 20 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "24.4",
      "12.1",
      "35.6",
      "20.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 45 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "5.87",
      "5.625",
      "15.97",
      "13.93"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.625"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 16 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "348",
      "320",
      "289",
      "360"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "320"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/3 \u00d7 2/9?",
    "answers": [
      "14/27",
      "42/81",
      "56/108",
      "28/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 11 = 19",
    "answers": [
      "-8",
      "8",
      "15",
      "34"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/8 \u00d7 3/4?",
    "answers": [
      "24/128",
      "18/96",
      "6/32",
      "12/64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/32"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 5?",
    "answers": [
      "-11",
      "53",
      "15",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 84 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "20.52",
      "13.57",
      "12.0",
      "6.02"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "261",
      "252",
      "240",
      "236"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 77 miles in 6 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "32.35",
      "12.833333333333334",
      "9.17",
      "19.64"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.833333333333334"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/1 \u00d7 9/1?",
    "answers": [
      "81/1",
      "324/4",
      "162/2",
      "243/3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "81/1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 11 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "171",
      "213",
      "143",
      "176"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "176"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 58 miles in 4 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "13.12",
      "21.97",
      "15.87",
      "14.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 22 miles in 9 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "15.11",
      "15.48",
      "9.47",
      "2.4444444444444446"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.4444444444444446"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "11",
      "60",
      "40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [17, 20, 13, 15, 6]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "55",
      "-26",
      "58"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 = 21",
    "answers": [
      "-20",
      "18",
      "62",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "79",
      "66",
      "92",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [1, 8, 4, 12, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "-11",
      "12",
      "-35",
      "-19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 15, 16, 5, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "53",
      "24",
      "16",
      "-9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/2 \u00d7 8/4?",
    "answers": [
      "24/24",
      "8/8",
      "32/32",
      "16/16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 20 = 23",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "-35",
      "-7",
      "3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 19 = 34",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "-11",
      "22",
      "59"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [19, 16, 17, 20, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "1",
      "40",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 20 = 28",
    "answers": [
      "35",
      "6",
      "8",
      "-9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 6 = 22",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "41",
      "7",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/8 \u00d7 5/9?",
    "answers": [
      "20/288",
      "15/216",
      "5/72",
      "10/144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5/72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/7 \u00d7 7/8?",
    "answers": [
      "126/112",
      "252/224",
      "189/168",
      "63/56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "63/56"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/1 \u00d7 7/6?",
    "answers": [
      "56/24",
      "42/18",
      "14/6",
      "28/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/7 \u00d7 2/9?",
    "answers": [
      "20/126",
      "10/63",
      "30/189",
      "40/252"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 17 = 29",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "17",
      "-18",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/5 \u00d7 1/9?",
    "answers": [
      "6/45",
      "12/90",
      "18/135",
      "24/180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/4 \u00d7 2/4?",
    "answers": [
      "10/16",
      "40/64",
      "20/32",
      "30/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10/16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/9 \u00d7 7/8?",
    "answers": [
      "84/288",
      "63/216",
      "42/144",
      "21/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "21/72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "187",
      "160",
      "206",
      "138"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "160"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 15",
    "answers": [
      "-28",
      "-21",
      "3",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 10 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "4.47",
      "4.64",
      "1.25",
      "10.06"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 19 = 25",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "-24",
      "6",
      "-13"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 16, 17, 19, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "-11",
      "17",
      "-9",
      "19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/7 \u00d7 4/4?",
    "answers": [
      "8/28",
      "16/56",
      "24/84",
      "32/112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "172",
      "238",
      "163",
      "192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "192"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 4 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "-24",
      "-34",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/9 \u00d7 9/4?",
    "answers": [
      "9/36",
      "18/72",
      "36/144",
      "27/108"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 22",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "-30",
      "60",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 6?",
    "answers": [
      "57",
      "88",
      "80",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 46 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "9.2",
      "14.09",
      "8.53",
      "17.94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/2 \u00d7 2/9?",
    "answers": [
      "36/36",
      "72/72",
      "18/18",
      "54/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/9 \u00d7 7/2?",
    "answers": [
      "14/18",
      "56/72",
      "42/54",
      "28/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/6 \u00d7 1/2?",
    "answers": [
      "6/12",
      "24/48",
      "12/24",
      "18/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/5 \u00d7 7/6?",
    "answers": [
      "140/120",
      "70/60",
      "35/30",
      "105/90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35/30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/9 \u00d7 4/2?",
    "answers": [
      "40/36",
      "60/54",
      "20/18",
      "80/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/6 \u00d7 1/9?",
    "answers": [
      "36/216",
      "27/162",
      "18/108",
      "9/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 8 = 21",
    "answers": [
      "-1",
      "41",
      "13",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 42 miles in 4 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "14.0",
      "27.1",
      "20.9",
      "10.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 12",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "32",
      "-44",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 5, 13, 1, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "56",
      "21",
      "34"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 5 = 12",
    "answers": [
      "-2",
      "7",
      "6",
      "-6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/8 \u00d7 8/5?",
    "answers": [
      "144/120",
      "192/160",
      "96/80",
      "48/40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48/40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 44 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "33.14",
      "22.0",
      "5.91",
      "16.74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 15 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "120",
      "147",
      "105",
      "145"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "105"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "48",
      "87",
      "83",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 4 and width 15?",
    "answers": [
      "60",
      "88",
      "35",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 93 miles in 6 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "14.19",
      "16.75",
      "12.95",
      "15.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 15 = 23",
    "answers": [
      "-26",
      "46",
      "8",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 19?",
    "answers": [
      "202",
      "228",
      "244",
      "188"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "228"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [4, 15, 20, 7, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "5",
      "4",
      "44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/5 \u00d7 7/9?",
    "answers": [
      "84/135",
      "28/45",
      "112/180",
      "56/90"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28/45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [13, 18, 19, 16, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "12",
      "56",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 38 miles in 10 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "6.64",
      "3.8",
      "2.35",
      "16.18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/1 \u00d7 6/3?",
    "answers": [
      "108/6",
      "162/9",
      "216/12",
      "54/3"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54/3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 68 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "27.65",
      "40.34",
      "22.666666666666668",
      "38.03"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "22.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 87 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "4.84",
      "19.74",
      "12.428571428571429",
      "25.46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 96 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "28.74",
      "29.98",
      "12.0",
      "7.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/5 \u00d7 9/5?",
    "answers": [
      "162/50",
      "243/75",
      "81/25",
      "324/100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "81/25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/2 \u00d7 5/3?",
    "answers": [
      "80/24",
      "60/18",
      "40/12",
      "20/6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 14 and width 19?",
    "answers": [
      "265",
      "266",
      "310",
      "248"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "266"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [12, 17, 13, 4, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "17",
      "34",
      "65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [13, 6, 13, 15, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "-11",
      "20",
      "4",
      "59"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [11, 5, 19, 5, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "33",
      "19",
      "52",
      "9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [9, 16, 11, 20, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "-4",
      "20",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 25",
    "answers": [
      "-14",
      "13",
      "-22",
      "37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/6 \u00d7 1/7?",
    "answers": [
      "18/84",
      "36/168",
      "9/42",
      "27/126"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [13, 11, 10, 17, 6]?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "5",
      "65",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 99 miles in 4 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "24.75",
      "17.29",
      "37.9",
      "25.42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 5?",
    "answers": [
      "67",
      "9",
      "50",
      "25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 5 = 15",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "46",
      "10",
      "-34"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 20 = 34",
    "answers": [
      "-36",
      "45",
      "14",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [12, 19, 7, 10, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "-10",
      "19",
      "-16",
      "-17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "54",
      "37",
      "15",
      "21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/8 \u00d7 8/6?",
    "answers": [
      "40/48",
      "160/192",
      "80/96",
      "120/144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [18, 20, 8, 20, 6]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "65",
      "-28",
      "47"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [5, 10, 16, 2, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "63",
      "17",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 83 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "39.18",
      "45.09",
      "41.5",
      "59.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "41.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 22",
    "answers": [
      "24",
      "22",
      "-16",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/2 \u00d7 9/5?",
    "answers": [
      "54/20",
      "81/30",
      "108/40",
      "27/10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27/10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 32 miles in 10 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "5.91",
      "6.93",
      "4.76",
      "3.2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 71 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "12.88",
      "2.15",
      "10.142857142857142",
      "6.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.142857142857142"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 8, 18, 6, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "56",
      "1",
      "18",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 14?",
    "answers": [
      "146",
      "166",
      "142",
      "140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 18 = 31",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "-29",
      "13",
      "-6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 84 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "35.09",
      "30.44",
      "42.0",
      "27.45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 28 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "2.93",
      "6.87",
      "12.29",
      "4.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 92 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "18.17",
      "30.666666666666668",
      "11.43",
      "17.54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/5 \u00d7 8/2?",
    "answers": [
      "224/40",
      "56/10",
      "112/20",
      "168/30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "56/10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 23 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "3.2857142857142856",
      "23.27",
      "15.15",
      "21.37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.2857142857142856"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [14, 6, 14, 2, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "-12",
      "-25",
      "14",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 19 and width 17?",
    "answers": [
      "284",
      "323",
      "370",
      "372"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "323"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/4 \u00d7 7/4?",
    "answers": [
      "42/16",
      "84/32",
      "168/64",
      "126/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42/16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 8",
    "answers": [
      "4",
      "28",
      "-11",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 10 = 21",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "11",
      "-8",
      "59"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 20 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "289",
      "211",
      "276",
      "240"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "84",
      "115",
      "127",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/6 \u00d7 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "120/18",
      "160/24",
      "40/6",
      "80/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 16 = 32",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "27",
      "35",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/3 \u00d7 9/8?",
    "answers": [
      "54/24",
      "162/72",
      "216/96",
      "108/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 82 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "82.0",
      "91.5",
      "88.86",
      "93.31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "82.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [5, 12, 9, 16, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "57",
      "48",
      "16",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [8, 16, 2, 5, 4]?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "60",
      "48",
      "16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 17 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "340",
      "336",
      "351",
      "366"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "340"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 7, 2, 10, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "-26",
      "0",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/8 \u00d7 7/5?",
    "answers": [
      "70/80",
      "105/120",
      "140/160",
      "35/40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35/40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 9 = 25",
    "answers": [
      "64",
      "-13",
      "16",
      "-24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 8?",
    "answers": [
      "39",
      "80",
      "115",
      "87"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/5 \u00d7 7/7?",
    "answers": [
      "42/105",
      "14/35",
      "28/70",
      "56/140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14/35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 86 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "22.55",
      "15.72",
      "28.666666666666668",
      "12.91"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 10?",
    "answers": [
      "29",
      "30",
      "22",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 6 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "155",
      "107",
      "120",
      "159"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 20 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "99",
      "181",
      "119",
      "140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 3 = 19",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "-4",
      "-24",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 21 miles in 9 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "10.84",
      "2.3333333333333335",
      "11.05",
      "20.95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.3333333333333335"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 8?",
    "answers": [
      "64",
      "81",
      "38",
      "106"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "64"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/7 \u00d7 1/9?",
    "answers": [
      "18/189",
      "6/63",
      "12/126",
      "24/252"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 87 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "12.428571428571429",
      "30.52",
      "5.44",
      "21.8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [1, 10, 6, 5, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "-9",
      "-26",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 13?",
    "answers": [
      "206",
      "179",
      "129",
      "156"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "156"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [16, 2, 14, 20, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "58",
      "-6",
      "20",
      "7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 9 = 16",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "7",
      "39",
      "12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/7 \u00d7 2/1?",
    "answers": [
      "8/28",
      "6/21",
      "4/14",
      "2/7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/7"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 8 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "-13",
      "-12",
      "-2",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/3 \u00d7 5/4?",
    "answers": [
      "50/24",
      "75/36",
      "25/12",
      "100/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 46 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "13.39",
      "7.41",
      "9.2",
      "28.94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 22 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "7.333333333333333",
      "6.39",
      "9.86",
      "6.54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.333333333333333"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 45 miles in 10 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "11.84",
      "4.5",
      "3.99",
      "16.71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 13 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "167",
      "191",
      "156",
      "199"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "156"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 4?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "52",
      "25",
      "48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 40 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "10.15",
      "6.87",
      "5.0",
      "15.58"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 22",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "42",
      "21",
      "-31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 19 and width 2?",
    "answers": [
      "-12",
      "76",
      "65",
      "38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "38"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 2 and width 15?",
    "answers": [
      "39",
      "19",
      "63",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 84 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "23.56",
      "44.78",
      "42.0",
      "37.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [20, 17, 13, 10, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "18",
      "7",
      "-8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 42 miles in 9 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "2.58",
      "4.666666666666667",
      "20.3",
      "17.16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.666666666666667"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/1 \u00d7 1/1?",
    "answers": [
      "16/2",
      "8/1",
      "24/3",
      "32/4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/1"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 19 miles in 6 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "17.66",
      "3.1666666666666665",
      "18.79",
      "20.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.1666666666666665"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 14 and width 7?",
    "answers": [
      "89",
      "52",
      "98",
      "144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "98"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [10, 15, 7, 4, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "15",
      "32",
      "-29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 20 and width 16?",
    "answers": [
      "348",
      "320",
      "362",
      "318"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "320"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [4, 9, 15, 9, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "-11",
      "56",
      "11",
      "15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 40 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "23.11",
      "24.74",
      "10.37",
      "5.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 20 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "240",
      "247",
      "243",
      "190"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 4 = 9",
    "answers": [
      "21",
      "-25",
      "26",
      "5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [20, 7, 2, 6, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "-15",
      "7",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/4 \u00d7 5/3?",
    "answers": [
      "20/12",
      "80/48",
      "40/24",
      "60/36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20/12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/3 \u00d7 2/8?",
    "answers": [
      "8/96",
      "2/24",
      "6/72",
      "4/48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [17, 5, 5, 19, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "19",
      "5",
      "36",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/7 \u00d7 1/3?",
    "answers": [
      "15/63",
      "10/42",
      "5/21",
      "20/84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5/21"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 92 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "54.23",
      "46.0",
      "46.26",
      "32.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "46.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 85 miles in 6 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "14.166666666666666",
      "31.98",
      "18.64",
      "16.39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.166666666666666"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 14 = 34",
    "answers": [
      "70",
      "16",
      "20",
      "65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [18, 5, 3, 10, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "44",
      "13",
      "36",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 29 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "24.47",
      "5.8",
      "24.68",
      "1.27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [4, 8, 12, 13, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "-19",
      "13",
      "-17",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 78 miles in 5 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "7.42",
      "15.6",
      "26.94",
      "26.88"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 13 and width 17?",
    "answers": [
      "196",
      "268",
      "246",
      "221"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "221"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [10, 11, 17, 17, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "34",
      "-19",
      "35",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 2 = 20",
    "answers": [
      "38",
      "-12",
      "43",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 15",
    "answers": [
      "-37",
      "8",
      "-18",
      "32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 4, 14, 13, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "-24",
      "14",
      "-7",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 15 and width 20?",
    "answers": [
      "281",
      "273",
      "282",
      "300"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "300"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [12, 6, 15, 7, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "35",
      "-5",
      "14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 15 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "41",
      "3",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/3 \u00d7 7/1?",
    "answers": [
      "140/12",
      "70/6",
      "35/3",
      "105/9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35/3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [3, 7, 19, 20, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "55",
      "46",
      "20",
      "-10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 11 = 13",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "14",
      "39",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/9 \u00d7 1/7?",
    "answers": [
      "4/126",
      "6/189",
      "2/63",
      "8/252"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "96",
      "126",
      "132",
      "62"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 13 and width 10?",
    "answers": [
      "109",
      "130",
      "121",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "130"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 5/8 \u00d7 5/2?",
    "answers": [
      "75/48",
      "100/64",
      "50/32",
      "25/16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25/16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 6, 15, 20, 3]?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "20",
      "44",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/4 \u00d7 2/1?",
    "answers": [
      "12/4",
      "48/16",
      "36/12",
      "24/8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12/4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 11 and width 4?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "44",
      "12",
      "42"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "44"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/1 \u00d7 9/3?",
    "answers": [
      "9/3",
      "27/9",
      "18/6",
      "36/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/3"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/8 \u00d7 4/9?",
    "answers": [
      "12/72",
      "24/144",
      "48/288",
      "36/216"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12/72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 9?",
    "answers": [
      "0",
      "19",
      "35",
      "27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "27"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/6 \u00d7 6/9?",
    "answers": [
      "72/216",
      "54/162",
      "36/108",
      "18/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18/54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 9/3 \u00d7 8/8?",
    "answers": [
      "144/48",
      "216/72",
      "72/24",
      "288/96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 11 = 19",
    "answers": [
      "49",
      "52",
      "8",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 12 and width 9?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "108",
      "151",
      "98"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [2, 16, 5, 16, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "-17",
      "16",
      "-11",
      "28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [15, 4, 7, 2, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "15",
      "17",
      "-30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 11 = 23",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "-32",
      "50",
      "61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 15 = 30",
    "answers": [
      "59",
      "31",
      "15",
      "60"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [20, 5, 5, 16, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "20",
      "68",
      "12",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/1 \u00d7 2/2?",
    "answers": [
      "6/6",
      "2/2",
      "8/8",
      "4/4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/2"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/9 \u00d7 1/7?",
    "answers": [
      "24/252",
      "6/63",
      "18/189",
      "12/126"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/63"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 58 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "14.95",
      "25.17",
      "6.7",
      "7.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "101",
      "96",
      "80",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [14, 7, 14, 7, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "31",
      "14",
      "24",
      "-33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 28",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "-28",
      "30",
      "-24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 19, 3, 13, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "-13",
      "19",
      "41",
      "-26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [11, 1, 16, 20, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "-10",
      "20",
      "1",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 31 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "6.62",
      "10.88",
      "4.428571428571429",
      "7.04"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 5 and width 17?",
    "answers": [
      "75",
      "62",
      "85",
      "124"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "85"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 14 = 24",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "-20",
      "-8",
      "11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 43 miles in 7 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "6.142857142857143",
      "16.62",
      "15.59",
      "8.45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.142857142857143"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/5 \u00d7 1/9?",
    "answers": [
      "32/180",
      "16/90",
      "8/45",
      "24/135"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/3 \u00d7 1/8?",
    "answers": [
      "2/24",
      "6/72",
      "4/48",
      "8/96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 53 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "7.58",
      "16.52",
      "17.666666666666668",
      "4.37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/7 \u00d7 5/5?",
    "answers": [
      "10/35",
      "40/140",
      "30/105",
      "20/70"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10/35"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [18, 17, 2, 17, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "-32",
      "-2",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [17, 10, 15, 12, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "17",
      "-18",
      "-6",
      "63"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 3 and width 15?",
    "answers": [
      "52",
      "33",
      "45",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [2, 20, 7, 9, 16]?",
    "answers": [
      "13",
      "8",
      "20",
      "69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 50 miles in 3 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "26.51",
      "28.44",
      "16.666666666666668",
      "30.95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 61 miles in 2 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "25.56",
      "30.5",
      "28.72",
      "35.11"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 5 = 9",
    "answers": [
      "-43",
      "-20",
      "17",
      "4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "4"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [17, 3, 3, 20, 4]?",
    "answers": [
      "-10",
      "35",
      "66",
      "20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 11, 6, 6, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "50",
      "-32",
      "-15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 19 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "268",
      "235",
      "228",
      "270"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "228"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [3, 12, 18, 8, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "47",
      "18",
      "52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 2/6 \u00d7 1/6?",
    "answers": [
      "6/108",
      "2/36",
      "8/144",
      "4/72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2/36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [11, 12, 12, 9, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "12",
      "-8",
      "-11",
      "-18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 75 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "74.37",
      "75.0",
      "83.7",
      "87.54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "75.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 13 and width 6?",
    "answers": [
      "60",
      "31",
      "78",
      "103"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "78"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [11, 19, 14, 6, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "-20",
      "19",
      "-9",
      "18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "19"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 3/3 \u00d7 3/6?",
    "answers": [
      "18/36",
      "9/18",
      "36/72",
      "27/54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9/18"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 100 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "100.0",
      "81.82",
      "88.49",
      "90.23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "100.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 17 and width 18?",
    "answers": [
      "266",
      "324",
      "306",
      "329"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "306"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 4 = 10",
    "answers": [
      "30",
      "6",
      "34",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [6, 5, 17, 16, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "9",
      "61",
      "17",
      "-1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [2, 5, 14, 2, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "-28",
      "22",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 7 = 18",
    "answers": [
      "-1",
      "31",
      "11",
      "-39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [9, 9, 2, 6, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "14",
      "13",
      "1"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [5, 7, 4, 10, 6]?",
    "answers": [
      "-10",
      "-30",
      "58",
      "10"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 19 = 31",
    "answers": [
      "59",
      "-27",
      "12",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 6/8 \u00d7 1/6?",
    "answers": [
      "6/48",
      "12/96",
      "18/144",
      "24/192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 18?",
    "answers": [
      "180",
      "144",
      "157",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "144"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 78 miles in 8 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "5.63",
      "27.12",
      "9.75",
      "10.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 83 miles in 9 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "23.48",
      "7.94",
      "9.222222222222221",
      "19.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.222222222222221"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 42 miles in 4 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "29.87",
      "1.03",
      "20.98",
      "10.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/6 \u00d7 8/8?",
    "answers": [
      "16/96",
      "24/144",
      "8/48",
      "32/192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8/48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 1/5 \u00d7 7/1?",
    "answers": [
      "28/20",
      "14/10",
      "21/15",
      "7/5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7/5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 68 miles in 1 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "68.0",
      "70.97",
      "56.86",
      "70.33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "68.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 13 and width 6?",
    "answers": [
      "78",
      "92",
      "117",
      "73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "78"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 7/5 \u00d7 6/3?",
    "answers": [
      "168/60",
      "42/15",
      "84/30",
      "126/45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42/15"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [8, 5, 20, 11, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "20",
      "24",
      "66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [5, 16, 1, 5, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "16",
      "-34",
      "51"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the maximum value in the set [13, 17, 5, 7, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "5",
      "10",
      "4",
      "17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 8/6 \u00d7 8/1?",
    "answers": [
      "128/12",
      "192/18",
      "64/6",
      "256/24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "64/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "A car travels 30 miles in 10 hours. What is the unit rate?",
    "answers": [
      "19.0",
      "16.99",
      "3.0",
      "10.16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 8 and width 17?",
    "answers": [
      "136",
      "86",
      "158",
      "149"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "136"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: x + 12 = 28",
    "answers": [
      "47",
      "16",
      "32",
      "-12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 10 and width 11?",
    "answers": [
      "110",
      "129",
      "96",
      "101"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "110"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the area of a rectangle with length 6 and width 12?",
    "answers": [
      "41",
      "72",
      "93",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is 4/6 \u00d7 5/1?",
    "answers": [
      "80/24",
      "20/6",
      "60/18",
      "40/12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20/6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.666666666666667",
      "3.72",
      "6.88",
      "13.88"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.666666666666667"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "211",
      "214",
      "216",
      "225"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [4, 16, 9, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.25",
      "21.5",
      "6.65",
      "9.79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "17.69",
      "8.3",
      "10.0",
      "28.81"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "54",
      "78",
      "25",
      "89"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "-21",
      "12",
      "16",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "152",
      "174",
      "170",
      "150"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "27.68",
      "11.428571428571429",
      "6.91",
      "13.76"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 1/10",
    "answers": [
      "20.0",
      "3.32",
      "34.83",
      "30.65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "-3",
      "24",
      "-20",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 1/10",
    "answers": [
      "96.26",
      "101.4",
      "90.0",
      "79.61"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "90.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 6, 16, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.75",
      "19.95",
      "5.6",
      "15.66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d79\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "330",
      "366",
      "378",
      "332"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "378"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 1/10",
    "answers": [
      "91.61",
      "108.23",
      "100.0",
      "92.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "100.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d77\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "343",
      "326",
      "332",
      "364"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "343"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "96",
      "92",
      "58",
      "101"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d76\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "162",
      "124",
      "158",
      "113"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "162"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d79\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "419",
      "405",
      "434",
      "433"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "405"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [4, 16, 8, 3]?",
    "answers": [
      "7.75",
      "5.38",
      "24.5",
      "19.19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d78\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "72",
      "77",
      "50",
      "106"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "18.84",
      "5.0",
      "9.07",
      "0.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [12, 9, 8, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "23.6",
      "14.77",
      "7.5",
      "8.17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d710\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "175",
      "197",
      "194",
      "180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "180"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [18, 14, 16, 3]?",
    "answers": [
      "0.15",
      "11.86",
      "18.56",
      "12.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [16, 15, 11, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "14.13",
      "4.8",
      "8.92",
      "14.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "50",
      "104",
      "31",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 8?",
    "answers": [
      "384",
      "338",
      "362",
      "421"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 4/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "5.714285714285714",
      "2.81",
      "23.61",
      "13.84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.714285714285714"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "127",
      "137",
      "53",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "603",
      "600",
      "643",
      "618"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "12.96",
      "9.61",
      "25.0",
      "14.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "25.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [15, 15, 2, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.25",
      "19.18",
      "10.28",
      "26.33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d710\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "362",
      "378",
      "350",
      "325"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "350"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d73\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "106",
      "60",
      "108",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "9.18",
      "22.9",
      "9.0",
      "25.94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "28.42",
      "15.35",
      "10.0",
      "26.08"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d77\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "186",
      "147",
      "189",
      "97"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "147"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.16",
      "10.85",
      "16.0",
      "19.29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "27.42",
      "40.96",
      "37.02",
      "45.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "216",
      "171",
      "209",
      "178"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "243",
      "216",
      "198",
      "246"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [6, 15, 5, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "22.86",
      "7.75",
      "26.81",
      "5.19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d710\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "628",
      "641",
      "620",
      "630"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "630"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d72\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "208",
      "228",
      "137",
      "180"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "180"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 1, 8, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "1.48",
      "26.44",
      "7.25",
      "25.32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "600",
      "612",
      "596",
      "633"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d73\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "-4",
      "44",
      "42",
      "72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [10, 7, 2, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.08",
      "8.25",
      "2.19",
      "6.02"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "26.77",
      "45.13",
      "45.0",
      "27.37"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "15.35",
      "1.1111111111111112",
      "4.63",
      "16.69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.1111111111111112"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d73\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "117",
      "165",
      "180",
      "150"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "99",
      "24",
      "54",
      "41"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d74\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "139",
      "75",
      "83",
      "120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d77\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "705",
      "690",
      "723",
      "700"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "700"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "68",
      "54",
      "73",
      "52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d75\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "360",
      "356",
      "316",
      "354"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "360"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "2.2",
      "31.06",
      "15.0",
      "14.04"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 8?",
    "answers": [
      "350",
      "384",
      "389",
      "336"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "61",
      "24",
      "-1",
      "-20"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [2, 13, 8, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.0",
      "28.41",
      "15.57",
      "21.73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [10, 20, 19, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "14.82",
      "16.0",
      "28.26",
      "31.49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d75\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "30",
      "-9",
      "-14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d77\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "328",
      "280",
      "258",
      "309"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "280"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "576",
      "600",
      "639",
      "607"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d76\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "473",
      "425",
      "390",
      "432"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "432"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "32.81",
      "26.06",
      "15.0",
      "32.97"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "9.33",
      "0.19",
      "11.11111111111111",
      "4.79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.11111111111111"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "32",
      "7",
      "2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d79\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "224",
      "201",
      "254",
      "243"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "243"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "12.48",
      "1.6666666666666667",
      "11.74",
      "6.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.6666666666666667"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.0",
      "6.38",
      "0.05",
      "23.85"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d73\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "-3",
      "38",
      "30",
      "8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d72\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "48",
      "15",
      "64",
      "94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [4, 11, 1, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "15.05",
      "2.6",
      "12.76",
      "6.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d79\u00d76 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "205",
      "191",
      "243",
      "216"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 19, 13, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "26.37",
      "17.25",
      "26.16",
      "33.31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "17.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "25.4",
      "12.857142857142858",
      "32.35",
      "4.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.857142857142858"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d73\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "48",
      "83",
      "19",
      "60"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "20.45",
      "9.81",
      "2.2222222222222223",
      "16.7"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.2222222222222223"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [17, 9, 6, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "21.89",
      "25.66",
      "8.5",
      "5.69"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "156",
      "179",
      "154",
      "150"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "-21",
      "45",
      "52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "15.23",
      "17.14",
      "9.86",
      "5.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d75\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "149",
      "78",
      "51",
      "100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "100"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "58",
      "69",
      "96",
      "115"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "96",
      "74",
      "77",
      "94"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "445",
      "493",
      "486",
      "529"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "2.857142857142857",
      "10.63",
      "8.83",
      "0.07"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.857142857142857"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [16, 18, 19, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "32.92",
      "32.55",
      "13.74",
      "15.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "1.63",
      "1.4285714285714286",
      "18.6",
      "11.03"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.4285714285714286"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "24",
      "-7",
      "49",
      "15"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.72",
      "11.9",
      "20.0",
      "1.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [11, 20, 11, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "26.71",
      "29.81",
      "15.5",
      "21.99"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "-1",
      "6",
      "-23",
      "33"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "5.555555555555555",
      "22.08",
      "24.28",
      "13.23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.555555555555555"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "630",
      "599",
      "600",
      "579"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "2.5",
      "19.01",
      "17.32",
      "5.24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 4/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "18.12",
      "25.48",
      "8.0",
      "3.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "11.95",
      "20.02",
      "14.8",
      "2.2222222222222223"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.2222222222222223"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "82",
      "96",
      "111",
      "67"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [14, 17, 13, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "12.64",
      "17.91",
      "13.75",
      "28.21"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "17.2",
      "14.285714285714286",
      "26.9",
      "11.56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.285714285714286"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d76\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "378",
      "409",
      "334",
      "420"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "378"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "41.43",
      "50.0",
      "49.23",
      "38.84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "17.12",
      "3.43",
      "15.0",
      "17.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d79\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "100",
      "143",
      "135",
      "110"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "135"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "19.03",
      "13.72",
      "7.65",
      "16.666666666666668"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d78\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "645",
      "657",
      "598",
      "648"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "648"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d78\u00d76 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "239",
      "173",
      "242",
      "192"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "192"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [1, 17, 17, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.5",
      "9.0",
      "27.42",
      "17.54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [9, 5, 10, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "16.04",
      "9.5",
      "12.24",
      "29.16"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d76\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "218",
      "133",
      "168",
      "129"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "168"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 4/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "19.46",
      "29.11",
      "10.0",
      "3.12"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.24",
      "13.333333333333334",
      "9.7",
      "10.39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.333333333333334"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [15, 11, 4, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "32.32",
      "1.89",
      "0.98",
      "12.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "50.0",
      "48.35",
      "62.13",
      "57.88"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "50.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d710\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "292",
      "318",
      "300",
      "252"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "300"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d75\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "16",
      "25",
      "40",
      "29"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [5, 15, 20, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "23.91",
      "13.75",
      "29.89",
      "4.52"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "486",
      "454",
      "487",
      "455"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "18",
      "54",
      "90",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d710\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "790",
      "800",
      "799",
      "846"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "800"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 4/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "23.76",
      "2.2",
      "8.16",
      "13.333333333333334"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.333333333333334"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.81",
      "6.08",
      "6.74",
      "1.4285714285714286"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.4285714285714286"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d710\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "60",
      "20",
      "82",
      "55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "60"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d76\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "157",
      "120",
      "134",
      "112"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "150",
      "191",
      "136",
      "127"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [2, 4, 12, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "18.23",
      "8.75",
      "24.26",
      "19.32"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "8.52",
      "26.19",
      "16.34",
      "10.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "18.75",
      "10.0",
      "22.34",
      "24.73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "4.77",
      "7.09",
      "16.0",
      "13.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.0",
      "2.35",
      "2.55",
      "14.79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "3.61",
      "12.67",
      "14.19",
      "2.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d76\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "491",
      "540",
      "552",
      "532"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "540"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "0.34",
      "18.18",
      "10.0",
      "5.82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "150",
      "128",
      "192",
      "195"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 1/10",
    "answers": [
      "28.8",
      "26.2",
      "16.75",
      "10.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "8.571428571428571",
      "20.16",
      "10.73",
      "6.46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.571428571428571"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "1.0",
      "18.4",
      "1.29",
      "11.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "1.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 8, 4, 19]?",
    "answers": [
      "6.17",
      "14.02",
      "12.5",
      "19.72"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "10",
      "8",
      "24",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.01",
      "2.5",
      "5.46",
      "12.35"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d73\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "2",
      "63",
      "23",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d78\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "640",
      "593",
      "676",
      "611"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "640"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d76\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "45",
      "46",
      "23",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "3.33",
      "10.0",
      "18.65",
      "9.56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d77\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "25",
      "70",
      "74",
      "43"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "70"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d72\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "14",
      "49",
      "12",
      "40"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d76\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "131",
      "132",
      "55",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "3.3333333333333335",
      "8.87",
      "1.09",
      "3.96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.3333333333333335"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d710\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "80",
      "67",
      "130",
      "38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "140",
      "150",
      "169",
      "175"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d78\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "279",
      "205",
      "240",
      "244"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d78\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "48",
      "15",
      "97",
      "82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "48"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d79\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "395",
      "405",
      "356",
      "417"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "405"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d72\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "43",
      "24",
      "34",
      "-2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "22.98",
      "6.8",
      "7.5",
      "20.66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "579",
      "569",
      "598",
      "600"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [13, 19, 16, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "24.09",
      "6.44",
      "15.75",
      "3.22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "4.92",
      "8.0",
      "11.66",
      "24.83"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "124",
      "154",
      "150",
      "170"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 7/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "34.31",
      "27.87",
      "23.333333333333332",
      "40.56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "23.333333333333332"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [9, 1, 18, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "17.76",
      "17.94",
      "19.95",
      "8.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "45.0",
      "56.05",
      "55.32",
      "25.26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [10, 16, 3, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.0",
      "20.45",
      "10.8",
      "11.44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [11, 1, 8, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.24",
      "6.25",
      "6.16",
      "3.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "25.71",
      "27.26",
      "33.32",
      "33.333333333333336"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "33.333333333333336"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d77\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "32",
      "75",
      "28",
      "68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "28"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "5.0",
      "23.03",
      "17.66",
      "10.19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 3, 6, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "16.71",
      "19.4",
      "7.25",
      "2.4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "471",
      "480",
      "462",
      "486"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "0.36",
      "20.0",
      "3.25",
      "17.44"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "45.0",
      "28.6",
      "28.49",
      "25.17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "9.0",
      "26.52",
      "8.03",
      "6.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [6, 18, 17, 16]?",
    "answers": [
      "14.69",
      "3.25",
      "26.12",
      "14.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d76\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "414",
      "387",
      "416",
      "384"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 7?",
    "answers": [
      "269",
      "279",
      "289",
      "294"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d78\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "128",
      "116",
      "108",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "128"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "150",
      "186",
      "121",
      "189"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "487",
      "534",
      "486",
      "441"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "514",
      "525",
      "486",
      "519"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "494",
      "490",
      "529",
      "486"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [12, 1, 19, 10]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.5",
      "6.2",
      "21.4",
      "12.2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "215",
      "216",
      "254",
      "258"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "40.0",
      "23.94",
      "24.25",
      "35.71"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [9, 9, 11, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "25.72",
      "14.08",
      "7.06",
      "11.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "7.5",
      "22.16",
      "8.87",
      "3.74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "22.8",
      "10.03",
      "16.43",
      "2.857142857142857"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "2.857142857142857"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d77\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "495",
      "502",
      "489",
      "504"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "504"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [8, 8, 3, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "14.53",
      "19.22",
      "9.75",
      "11.66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d79\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "630",
      "588",
      "590",
      "591"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "630"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d78\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "224",
      "223",
      "226",
      "232"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "224"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [10, 19, 5, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "10.03",
      "8.75",
      "5.15",
      "24.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [6, 20, 18, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "26.95",
      "12.39",
      "11.25",
      "24.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 14, 12, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "0.8",
      "16.25",
      "3.15",
      "29.14"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "646",
      "637",
      "631",
      "600"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 8?",
    "answers": [
      "421",
      "346",
      "397",
      "384"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [7, 6, 12, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "20.15",
      "8.59",
      "7.86",
      "9.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "600",
      "637",
      "588",
      "567"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "54",
      "64",
      "94",
      "74"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "14",
      "8",
      "24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "-35",
      "40",
      "6",
      "-34"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "522",
      "452",
      "484",
      "486"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "29.65",
      "20.0",
      "16.01",
      "39.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d77\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "140",
      "116",
      "117",
      "102"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d78\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "237",
      "169",
      "216",
      "199"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 7?",
    "answers": [
      "296",
      "334",
      "249",
      "294"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "532",
      "486",
      "460",
      "512"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d72\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "49",
      "80",
      "83",
      "109"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "80"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "620",
      "596",
      "600",
      "599"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d74\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "101",
      "72",
      "102",
      "58"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [4, 8, 17, 16]?",
    "answers": [
      "25.77",
      "2.5",
      "3.29",
      "11.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [14, 8, 15, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "5.09",
      "13.13",
      "3.82",
      "10.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [12, 8, 8, 9]?",
    "answers": [
      "8.41",
      "16.82",
      "21.0",
      "9.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d79\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "64",
      "74",
      "82",
      "108"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "108"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 7/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "7.777777777777778",
      "24.86",
      "16.94",
      "1.49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.777777777777778"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [4, 3, 7, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "23.65",
      "5.64",
      "19.96",
      "3.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d79\u00d76 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "364",
      "378",
      "375",
      "383"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "378"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d73\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "8",
      "78",
      "83",
      "36"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 7/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.17",
      "7.777777777777778",
      "23.29",
      "19.48"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.777777777777778"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d76\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "509",
      "582",
      "528",
      "540"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "540"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "25.95",
      "20.73",
      "16.666666666666668",
      "33.45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "20.14",
      "26.666666666666668",
      "15.75",
      "17.46"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "15",
      "-18",
      "24",
      "23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [11, 13, 2, 8]?",
    "answers": [
      "26.9",
      "8.5",
      "18.15",
      "24.4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "108",
      "47",
      "137",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [20, 17, 10, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "12.89",
      "15.0",
      "1.84",
      "21.03"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [12, 13, 4, 6]?",
    "answers": [
      "25.99",
      "8.75",
      "14.83",
      "1.24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "7.31",
      "9.5",
      "16.666666666666668",
      "26.02"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [5, 13, 7, 1]?",
    "answers": [
      "6.5",
      "14.5",
      "11.45",
      "6.18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 1/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "20.87",
      "6.89",
      "3.3333333333333335",
      "22.17"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.3333333333333335"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 8?",
    "answers": [
      "396",
      "415",
      "384",
      "434"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d74\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "142",
      "189",
      "181",
      "140"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [2, 8, 17, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "16.2",
      "28.73",
      "10.19",
      "11.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "600",
      "636",
      "606",
      "634"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.0",
      "11.16",
      "18.71",
      "18.84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 9/10",
    "answers": [
      "13.18",
      "4.72",
      "18.11",
      "5.555555555555555"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.555555555555555"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d74\u00d710 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "166",
      "112",
      "164",
      "160"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "160"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "196",
      "248",
      "216",
      "185"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d77\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "120",
      "140",
      "155",
      "163"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "140"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [15, 11, 3, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "27.33",
      "14.54",
      "11.75",
      "11.18"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 7?",
    "answers": [
      "268",
      "260",
      "272",
      "294"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "0.74",
      "0.09",
      "10.23",
      "3.75"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "11.44",
      "20.0",
      "31.59",
      "23.84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d74\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "122",
      "97",
      "72",
      "56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d72\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "73",
      "21",
      "74",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "49",
      "53",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "45",
      "17",
      "31",
      "6"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d73\u00d76 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "36",
      "45",
      "57",
      "39"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "36"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [1, 7, 16, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.82",
      "10.91",
      "9.0",
      "21.02"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "72",
      "96",
      "128",
      "100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "19.3",
      "26.666666666666668",
      "29.63",
      "21.55"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "26.666666666666668"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d79\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "214",
      "194",
      "252",
      "216"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "10.12",
      "16.88",
      "14.285714285714286",
      "29.2"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.285714285714286"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "30.0",
      "12.68",
      "20.16",
      "46.95"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "30.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 9?",
    "answers": [
      "453",
      "510",
      "486",
      "477"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "486"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d74\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "135",
      "192",
      "113",
      "160"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "160"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d73\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "176",
      "201",
      "186",
      "189"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "189"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "259",
      "189",
      "216",
      "222"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [16, 6, 5, 4]?",
    "answers": [
      "13.45",
      "7.75",
      "2.25",
      "22.09"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "13.39",
      "8.571428571428571",
      "24.73",
      "8.84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "8.571428571428571"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "600",
      "582",
      "645",
      "581"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d78\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "192",
      "142",
      "122",
      "144"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "144"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 3?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "12",
      "52",
      "54"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "54"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 7?",
    "answers": [
      "294",
      "293",
      "303",
      "291"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d73\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "63",
      "55",
      "133",
      "84"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "84"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d75\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "45",
      "24",
      "58",
      "73"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "45"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d78\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "485",
      "451",
      "413",
      "448"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "448"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "18.06",
      "10.0",
      "7.24",
      "21.09"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 9\u00d78\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "376",
      "360",
      "327",
      "373"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "360"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d77\u00d76 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "252",
      "261",
      "254",
      "273"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "252"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "5.0",
      "7.93",
      "5.85",
      "4.19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d73\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "147",
      "128",
      "112",
      "120"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [5, 14, 17, 14]?",
    "answers": [
      "17.18",
      "12.5",
      "22.05",
      "31.22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 2\u00d710\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "40",
      "13",
      "-4",
      "0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "40"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "-39",
      "6",
      "19",
      "22"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "23.85",
      "17.01",
      "24.24",
      "10.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [13, 19, 3, 20]?",
    "answers": [
      "22.81",
      "3.07",
      "13.75",
      "23.06"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "-10",
      "24",
      "-23",
      "-19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [8, 14, 1, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "6.25",
      "4.18",
      "9.69",
      "15.78"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d76\u00d77 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "320",
      "294",
      "323",
      "338"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [5, 5, 7, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "5.5",
      "8.56",
      "15.63",
      "16.4"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "108",
      "150",
      "136",
      "154"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d78\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "100",
      "26",
      "72",
      "82"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "72"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [14, 11, 19, 18]?",
    "answers": [
      "7.32",
      "15.5",
      "27.21",
      "28.65"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "15.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "37",
      "35",
      "6",
      "-28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "113",
      "165",
      "102",
      "150"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 7?",
    "answers": [
      "248",
      "294",
      "317",
      "252"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "294"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [2, 8, 15, 15]?",
    "answers": [
      "0.16",
      "13.64",
      "10.0",
      "1.77"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 3/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.666666666666667",
      "3.56",
      "20.8",
      "2.8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.666666666666667"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "17.96",
      "23.14",
      "17.1",
      "11.25"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [19, 17, 5, 11]?",
    "answers": [
      "0.45",
      "13.0",
      "13.67",
      "31.96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "13.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 7\u00d76\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "324",
      "288",
      "336",
      "361"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "336"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "600",
      "636",
      "649",
      "561"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d710\u00d79 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "506",
      "557",
      "528",
      "540"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "540"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 8/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "30.13",
      "9.01",
      "16.94",
      "11.428571428571429"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.428571428571429"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d77\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "168",
      "148",
      "201",
      "209"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "168"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "-22",
      "6",
      "19",
      "26"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 3\u00d77\u00d72 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "42",
      "51",
      "37",
      "23"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "42"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [11, 14, 18, 5]?",
    "answers": [
      "12.27",
      "18.3",
      "12.0",
      "14.68"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d78\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "308",
      "280",
      "297",
      "320"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "320"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 2?",
    "answers": [
      "71",
      "59",
      "24",
      "38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "24"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 5?",
    "answers": [
      "116",
      "128",
      "182",
      "150"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "150"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "227",
      "216",
      "255",
      "169"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [13, 10, 12, 7]?",
    "answers": [
      "3.03",
      "20.72",
      "0.41",
      "10.5"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "6.0",
      "7.3",
      "22.98",
      "13.9"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [16, 8, 2, 12]?",
    "answers": [
      "9.5",
      "5.18",
      "5.34",
      "7.05"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "9.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d76\u00d74 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "240",
      "234",
      "223",
      "280"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [20, 10, 18, 2]?",
    "answers": [
      "12.25",
      "12.5",
      "8.93",
      "11.79"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 4?",
    "answers": [
      "82",
      "107",
      "98",
      "96"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "96"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 3/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "3.75",
      "19.67",
      "11.82",
      "19.38"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 4\u00d710\u00d73 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "132",
      "120",
      "148",
      "100"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "120"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [13, 14, 11, 13]?",
    "answers": [
      "12.75",
      "19.03",
      "8.18",
      "24.58"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "12.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 10/10",
    "answers": [
      "9.33",
      "10.0",
      "7.5",
      "15.51"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [8, 17, 17, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "1.82",
      "14.75",
      "28.21",
      "22.24"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "14.75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [17, 11, 19, 17]?",
    "answers": [
      "19.33",
      "5.13",
      "0.19",
      "16.0"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "16.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 9/x = 8/10",
    "answers": [
      "11.25",
      "15.0",
      "6.16",
      "28.91"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "11.25"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 7/x = 2/10",
    "answers": [
      "43.44",
      "26.5",
      "35.0",
      "39.97"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "35.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 5\u00d73\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "125",
      "54",
      "75",
      "30"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "75"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 10?",
    "answers": [
      "602",
      "593",
      "645",
      "600"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "600"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 6?",
    "answers": [
      "216",
      "184",
      "185",
      "239"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "216"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 8?",
    "answers": [
      "390",
      "429",
      "392",
      "384"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "384"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 6\u00d78\u00d75 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "248",
      "224",
      "240",
      "237"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "240"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 10\u00d710\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "800",
      "839",
      "804",
      "786"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "800"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "21",
      "10",
      "6",
      "45"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "-29",
      "33",
      "-19"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 5/x = 7/10",
    "answers": [
      "23.91",
      "25.08",
      "7.142857142857143",
      "17.56"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "7.142857142857143"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 6/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "15.35",
      "18.21",
      "10.0",
      "28.49"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 6/10",
    "answers": [
      "3.3333333333333335",
      "13.22",
      "8.02",
      "16.27"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "3.3333333333333335"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the mean of [2, 12, 12, 16]?",
    "answers": [
      "18.66",
      "18.91",
      "10.5",
      "29.66"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "10.5"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the volume of a 8\u00d72\u00d78 rectangular prism?",
    "answers": [
      "136",
      "120",
      "168",
      "128"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "128"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 10/x = 5/10",
    "answers": [
      "22.67",
      "28.04",
      "20.0",
      "11.28"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "20.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "Solve: 2/x = 4/10",
    "answers": [
      "12.56",
      "9.03",
      "5.0",
      "3.31"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "5.0"
  },
  {
    "grade": 6,
    "subject": "Math",
    "question": "What is the surface area of a cube with side 1?",
    "answers": [
      "6",
      "24",
      "45",
      "-8"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": "6"
  }
]